A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Corporation, Board of Trustees, Finance Committee FA1007
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University records, Corporation, Board of Trustees, Finance Committee
1967-1997
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University
FA1007
3.6 Cubic Feet 3 record storage cartons.
3 record storage cartons.
Conditions Governing Access
Records more than 25 years old are open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Other Finding Aids
For Finance Committee records currently open for scholarly research see:
FA1017 Rockefeller University records, Corporation, Board of Trustees, Finance Committee, Minutes
File Plan
Former Classification: I 140-U
Arrangement
Primarily chronological
Scope and Contents
Contains Finance Committee meeting records, agendas, minutes, correspondence and associated financial reports.
- Finance Committee, Fiscal Year (FY) 1967 July-1968 June (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Finance Committee, FY 1968 July-1969 June (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Finance Committee, FY 1969 July-1970 June (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Finance Committee, FY 1970 July-1971 June (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Financial Report Supplement, 1971 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Finance Committee, 1971 July-1972 June (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Finance Committee, 1972 May 17 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Finance Committee, FY 1972 July-1973 June (Box 1, Folder 8-9)
- Analysis of financial resources, 1973 May 3 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Financial Report Supplement, 1973 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Finance Committee, FY 1974 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Financial Report Supplement, 1974 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Committee for the Future of the University (Haggerty Committee), 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 14, Box 2, Folder 1-4)
- Finance Committee, FY 1975 (Box 2, Folder 5-6)
- Finance Committee, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 7-10)
- Proceedings of seminar for trustees of educational institutions, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Financial Report Supplement, 1977 June 30 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Finance Committee, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 13-14)
- Joint Finance and Budget Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Finance Committee, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Finance Committee, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- New York State Coalition for Independent Colleges and Universities, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Finance Committee, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 3-5)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted from scholarly research - Open in 2017
- Finance Committee, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Restricted from scholarly research - Open in 2018
- Finance Committee, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 7-8)
  Restricted from scholarly access - Open in 2019
- Development and Academic Planning Files, 1990-1993 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Finance Committee, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Restricted from scholarly access - Open in 2020
- Finance Committee, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Restricted from scholarly access - Open in 2021
- Finance Committee, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 12-13)
  Restricted from scholarly access - Open in 2022
- Finance Committee and Audit Files, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 14-17)
  Restricted from scholarly access - Open in 2024